tomodo.com 2014-07-01

# TOMODO

## Privacy Policy

Last Revised: 18/8/2013

  1. Introduction

1.1. We, TOMODO Ltd. ("We", "Us", or "Our"), respect the privacy of the users and visitors of Our crowd sourcing platform ("Platform") and/or service ("Service"), and are committed to protect the information that Our users ("User" or "You") share with Us. 

1.2. We believe that You have the right to know our practices regarding the information We may collect when You log into the Platform and use the Service. The guidelines contained herein apply to your use of the Platform and/or Service

1.3. PLEASE READ CAREFULLY: BY USING THE PLATFORM AND/OR SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE APPLICATION OR THE SERVICE.

  2. Which information may we collect with regards to Our Users?

2.1. We collect two types of data and information:

2.1.1. Non-identifiable and anonymous information ("Non-personal Information"). To put it simply, we have no idea what is the identity of the User from which we have collected the Non-personal Information. The Non-personal Information We gather consists of technical information and behavioral information, including, among others, the following:

Technical information:

    * IP address (e.g. 208.77.188.166)

Behavioral information:

    * Favorable Mods
    * Favorable features
    * Favorable Sites

2.1.2. Individually identifiable information ("Personal Information") - To put it simple, this information may identify an individual or is of a private and/or sensitive nature. The Personal Information gathered consists of personal details You have provided us through the Account Registration Procedure, via email and/or which is available through Your profile in one of the social media platforms through which You have logged into the Platform, including, but not limited to: Facebook, and LinkedIn. The Personal Information gathered consists of individually identifiable information, including, but not limited to Your full name and e-mail address. How do we collect information on our Users? 

We collect information through Your use of the Platform and/or Service. In other words, when You use the Platform and/or Service We are aware of Your usage of the Platform and/or Service and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage.

  3. What are the purposes of the collection of information?

3.1. Non-personal Information is collected in order to learn about general trends on Our Platform and/or Service, and enhance the User's experience of the Platform and/or Service (We determine the Users' preferences, the favorite sites, etc.).

3.2. Personal Information is accessed in order to provide You with certain services, including sending You updates regarding the Platform and/or Service

  4. Sharing information with third parties

WE WILL NEVER SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION EXCEPT FOR THE FOLLOWING CASES: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce these Privacy Policy, and the TOMODO Terms of Use, as applicable, including investigation of potential violations of them; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to claims that any content published on the Platform and/or Service, including, but not limited to, any content which appears in any of the Mods, violates any right of a third-party; (e) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. phone number, name, etc.) of a third-party has been posted on the Platform and/or Service or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (f) to protect Our rights, property, or personal safety and those of our users or the general public; (g) if We undergo any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of Our assets of Company; (h) in order to provide You with Our services and with related services; or (i) pursuant to Your approval, in order to supply certain services the You have requested from Us.

  5. Deletion/Modification of Personal Information

At any time You may request that Your User's Information would be deleted or modified, in whole or in part, by sending an email to [info@tomodo.com](mailto:info@tomodo.com). 

  6. Cookies & Local Storage

When You use the Platform and/or the Service, We may use industry-standard technologies such as "cookies", Flash and/or Silverlight (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer ("Tracking Cookie(s)") and which will allow Us to enable automatic sign-in to the Platform and/or Service and make the User's browsing more convenient and effortless. It is easy to prohibit the Tracking Cookie option. Most browsers will allow the User to erase cookies from their computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. In order to erase or disable the Tracking Cookie option in Flash or Silverlight You should use the settings option of Flash/Silverlight according to the specific instructions provided by the technology provider. However, if You block or erase Tracking Cookies, or change the settings of Flash and/or Silverlight, Your online experience may be limited.

  7. Security

We take a great care in maintaining the security of Our Platform, Service and Users' information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through industry standard technologies and internal procedures. However, We do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.

  8. Changes to the Privacy Policy

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use the Platform and/or Service and any information collected therein. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, so the User is encouraged to re-visit this page frequently. In case of any material change, we may post a clear notice on the Application. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated "Last Update" and your continued use of the Platform and/or Service on or after the Last Update date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

  9. Questions

For any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, please send Us an email to the following address: [info@tomodo.com](mailto:info@tomodo.com) , and We will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe.
